Guard, halt.
立定
Handcuffs.
手銬
Left turn.
向左轉
Corporal.
下士
Come on, let's have you! Get fell in!
快，出來！ 出來列隊！
It's roll call! Let's have you!
出來點名！ 出來！
- Sergeant, check the other huts. - Quick march, double!
-軍士，看看其它房間 -跑步！
Come on! Move! Move!
快！跟上！跟上！
Come on! Fall out for roll call, or it's blood for breakfast!
聽到沒？！出來點名 否則早餐要喝血了！
Kapitan Schleutter's compliments to Major Perry.
Schleutter上尉有話給佩裡上校
He will speak only to the Major.
他只和上校談
The P.A.
話筒給我
Captain Schleutter, your men will now fall in for roll call...
Schleutter上尉, 你的人 必須出來集合點名
and 25 of them will be handcuffed, as previously ordered.
其中25人要帶手銬 這是必須的
Your country started this in violating the Geneva Convention.
你的國家違反日內瓦協議 挑起這一切
Twenty-five British officers were shackled...
在德國的 Ludwigsdorf 監獄 25名英國軍官
in Ludwigsdorf Prison in Germany.
被帶了手銬
After roll call, we must handcuff 25 of your officers...
點名後，必須銬起來25名軍官
Captain Schleutter.
Schleutter上尉
How do you plan to do that, Major?
你準備怎麼做呢, 上校?
There are 600 of us and we don't agree.
我們有600個人，我們不同意
You leave me no alternative but to result to force.
你是在逼我用暴力
Bloody man. I mean, can't he see?
好鬥的傢伙，是吧?
There's nothing for it.
毫無意義
- Bring 'em up. - Yes, sir.
- 帶他們過來 - 是，長官
Major Cox, bring those men up here.
考科斯上校, 把那些人帶到這裡
Squad, mark time!
原地踏步!
Squad, halt!
立定!
Sir!
長官!
Mr. Cox, enter barracks number one...
考科斯先生, 進入一號房
and place Captain Schleutter under arrest.
逮捕Schleutter上尉
Y es, sir! Gates!
是, 長官! 開門!
Company, double march!
跑步，走!
Come on, let's go!
來呀, 我們走!
I want no part of this, understand?
我不參與，明白嗎？
All guard towers...
衛兵聽著...
this is Major Perry.
這是佩裡上校
There is to be no shooting...
不要開槍...
unless a prisoner crosses the trip wire.
除非犯人越過警戒線
Is that understood?
明白嗎?
Cease firing.
停火
Come out, you kraut swine!
出來, 你這德國髒豬!
Why don't you come in here?!
你幹嗎不進來?!
Bastards!
狗娘養的!
Gas grenades in.
催淚彈準備
Tear gas, they're past the wire.
催淚彈, 他們過線了
Come on! Double it up!
快! 快點!
I want 12 men. Six with me and six around the back.
我要12個人 6人跟著我，6人去後面
Those men, pronto! Cover the other side!
快速行動! 去另一邊!
Drop back and form a line!
退後站成一線!
Fix bayonets!
上刺刀!
All guard towers...
塔樓士兵聽著...
there is to be no shooting unless they cross the trip wire.
他們越過警戒線就開槍
Soldiers, stand guard!
士兵, 站好崗位!
Move it up!
衝上去!
Hurry up! Get in there! Go round that side.
快! 去那裡! 圍住那邊
Is the Luftwaffe...above all this.
是德國空軍...關鍵時候
Come on - get going.
快 - 走啊
Go to the devil.
去死吧
What a bunch of idiots.
真是一群傻蛋
Get the Tommies out of here. Out!...Out!...Out!
把英國兵弄出去 出去!...出去!...出去!
Close the gates!
關上門!
Send your handcuffs back to London, Major Perry.
把你的手拷送回倫敦吧, 佩裡上校
Captain Schleutter, I'm entitled by the Geneva Convention...
Schleutter上尉 日內瓦協議授權與我
to punish you and your men for this incredible behavior!
懲罰你們這怪誕的行為!
You'll be confined to your huts on restricted diet for 48 hours!
你們將被限食限行動48小時
All privileges and electric power...
所有的優待及電力
will be curtailed for that period.
將被縮減
And at the end of that period...
限制結束後
you will fall in for roll call in proper order.
你們要有秩序地集合點名
As indeed you are now.
就像現在這樣
Send your handcuffs back to London and stay out of our camp until you do.
把你的手拷送回倫敦 否則離開我們的營地
Did you have relations with an enlisted personnel...
你和某個軍人發生關係
Captain Connor?
康納上尉?
I did, sir.
是的, 長官
She was willing.
她是自願的
Did you strike an officer of His Majesty's Navy?
你是否打了海軍軍官？
Not at all. I said something or other.
沒有，我只說了些事
He gave me a sort of push. It wasn't anything.
他推了我一下，沒什麼
The police report called it "aggravated assault."
警察報告中寫著 「惡化事態的攻擊」
Did it?
是嗎?
Your past record indicates that you were...
記錄顯示你是
drunk with four enlisted men...
和4個軍人喝醉了...
and absent without leave...
擅離職守
six times.
6次
Even though you are currently awaiting orders for your next posting...
現在你等候調職
that is not a license to ignore military regulations...
並不是說可以忽視條例...
and bring disgrace to the uniform.
給軍隊帶來恥辱
Yes, sir.
是, 長官
It is within the authority of this review board...
根據記錄
to reduce you in rank to the lowest commissioned rating.
要降低你的職位使用
However, we have been requested to hold our decision in abeyance...
然而，我們應情報部要求
by His Majesty's lntelligence.
暫停處理
- General Kerr wishes to question you. - Ben Kerr?
- 克爾將軍有話問你 - 是本•克爾?
So it's a balls-up again, eh, Jack?
又亂套了不是，傑克？
The army must be in a bad way for generals, makin' you one.
將軍總是覺得軍隊糟糕才像個將軍
- You've got that bit right at least. - What's an editor do in the army?
- 你總算明白了些 - 一個編輯在軍隊能幹什麼?
Write stories about Hitler's sex life and send 'em off to the newspapers?
寫希特勒的性生活然後發給報紙？
We put corrupt and ill-assorted talents like yours to work winning the war.
我們讓像你這樣的怪才歪才工作 來贏得戰爭
I've requested your transfer to lntelligence.
我已要求調你來情報部
Why in hell you want to do that?
你怎麼會這樣做？
You're going to run a P.O.W. camp in Scotland.
你去管理蘇格蘭的戰俘營
God, Benny. I'm not a policeman.
饒了我吧，本。我不是警察
Damn good crime reporter, though.
去你的好記者吧！
You've been a chaotic bastard for as long as I've known you.
自從我認識你 你就是個不安分的傢伙
But you have a perverse sort of genius for setting things in order around you--
但你總是有不正當的天賦 把周圍的事情理順
when you've a mind to.
只要你有心去做
I've a mind to go on a holiday at the moment.
我現在有心去度假
Well, that review board will see that you get it.
記錄裡說你度過假了
Jack, I'm saving your royal lrish ass for you...
傑克, 我是在救你這高貴的愛爾蘭蠢蛋
and giving you the chance to do the sort of job you've always been keen on doing.
讓你有機會做適合你的工作
Prisoners of war? I puke, sir.
戰俘? 我吐, 長官
Now get stuffed, Jack.
別廢話了, 傑克.
I need you. I need your great nose to the ground.
我需要你，我非常需要你那非凡的感應力
The German prisoners, all top-line officers...
McKenzie的德軍戰俘, 全是高級官員
have been raising a peculiar sort of hell at McKenzie the past few months.
在過去幾個月裡一直在製造麻煩
Other camps, relative quiet.
其它地方相對平靜
McKenzie, veritable state of siege.
McKenzie, 實際上是失控
Both War Office and lntelligence want to find out if there's any connection...
作戰部和情報部都想知道他們
any link with the dear old Deutschland.
是否與德國有聯繫
You have full authorization...
你被授全權
to do what you must to bring the camp around...
做任何必做之事 恢復營地的秩序
and find out what we need to know.
找出我們想知道的
A Major Perry's in command there.
佩裡上校現負責那裡
The captain tells the major how to run his camp?
讓上尉指揮上校管理營地？
I thought that would amuse you.
那讓你好笑吧
He'll be instructed to cooperate with Military lntelligence and so on.
他將收到指令和情報部合作
What about that review board?
那記錄怎麼處理?
Have you any ideas how to keep them off my back?
你有辦法不讓那來騷擾我嗎？
I shall ponder the matter, old boy.
我會處理的，老傢伙
Can you give me something for diarrhea...
能來點治痢疾
headache or constipation?
頭痛或便秘的嗎？
Y es, here he comes-- Major Perry!
好的, 他來了-- 佩裡上校!
English. English.
說英語
Why are those boys fighting?
為什麼那些孩子打鬥？
Why does that schoolmaster not stop them?
為什麼校長不制止他們？
Here he comes-- Major Perry!
他來了--佩裡上校!
Quiet...quiet. There's more to come.
安靜...安靜 還有節目
The next one who whistles will be fined 10 marks.
誰再吹口哨將罰款10馬克
All the English have fat asses
英國人都有個肥屁股
Major Perry, Sergeant Cox
佩裡上校, 考科斯軍士
We would like to give them handcuffs
我們想給他們帶手銬
Put them in a six-feet box
把他們關進6英尺的箱子
When the war is gone and finished
當戰爭結束
And we win the victory
我們贏得勝利
Deutschland then will be much bigger
德國將會更大
England then belongs to you and me
英格蘭則屬於你和我
When the war is gone and finished
當戰爭結束
And we win the victory
我們贏得勝利
Deutschland then will be much bigger
德國將會更大
England then belongs to you and me
英格蘭則屬於你和我
We can stay in Camp McKenzie
我們可留在McKenzie戰俘營
For England then belongs to you and me
因為英格蘭屬於你和我
Three cheers for Commandant Schluetter...
為司令官Schluetter歡呼
...hip hip, hooray.
...萬歲
It's a bloody English music hall.
這是個血腥的英國雜耍戲院
Is more fun in here without the English Tommies, eh?
沒有英國兵能有意思嗎？
All of you - thanks for this morning.
你們 - 謝謝今早演出
You make a lousy English lady, Schmidt.
你扮了個噁心的英國女人, Schmidt
She's too Jewish looking!
她太像猶太人了！
Neuchl, you should take the part.
Neuchl, 你應該參加
You'd make a hell of an English lady.
你扮來一定很像英國女人
Why not bring your friend, Berger, up here to the stage...
為何不帶你的朋友Berger到台上來
and do the sketch for us like two English ladies?
給我們模仿兩個英國女人的做派?
Won't you?
行嗎?
Your position, Kapitan, is not so to give me such insult.
你的地位並不是用來這樣侮辱我的
My position as your commanding officer is so...
作為你的長官，我的地位是...
to have you killed for being a coward, if I must.
因懦弱槍斃你
Are you not a coward?
你不是懦夫嗎?
I obey the rules of a prisoner of war.
我遵守戰犯規則
As the German Camp Commandant...
做為德國戰俘營司令官...
...you know the Geneva Convention forbids you to incite a riot.
...你知道日內瓦協議不允許煽動騷亂
You are a homosexual, are you not?
你是個同性戀，不是嗎？
Sorry. Your English is poor.
對不起. 你英語很差
You're a queer aren't you?
你是個同性戀，是不是?
Why don't you ask Berger here to the stage?
為何不讓Berger上台來？
You can hug and kiss and have a lovely queer wedding.
你們可擁抱接吻 來一個可愛的同性戀婚禮
I'll see you later.
我會再找你的
To hell with orders, let's make a victory fire.
去他的規定吧 讓我們點起勝利之火
Quite right, Mr. Cox. Fireworks night.
是的, 考科斯先生 煙火之夜
They're flaunting the blackout regulations, sir.
他們在蔑視燈火管制
Yes, celebrating my 48-hour punishment.
是的，慶祝48小時的處罰
- We'll see to that, sir. - You'll see to what?
- 我們等著看吧 - 等著看什麼?
You'll see to it that we're all made fools of once again.
等著看我們又被耍了一次
Will you move men in there to enforce blackout regulations?
你不能派人去執行燈火管制嗎？
Jerry will have disappeared by the time you get there, laughing at us.
等到那裡，他們會都跑了，又笑話我們
Your men will get a few more broken heads for their pains.
你的人會少幾個頭被打破的
The bleeding krauts are lightin' up the sky askin' for a raid, sir.
這幫好鬥的德國佬點火指引空襲
There's never been a raid within 100 miles of this desolate chicken farm!
在這荒涼的雞場100英里範圍內 從沒有過空襲!
Only alerts. I mean, why bomb this?
只有警報 我是說, 怎麼會炸這裡呢?
This understaffed, ill-manned outpost of military mediocrities.
這裡人員不足、設備簡陋 很平常的邊區村落
Thank you. That'll be all.
謝謝，沒事的
Make transport arrangements for a Captain Connor coming up from London.
安排一下從倫敦來的康納上尉
- The details are in the orderly room. - Yes, sir.
- 詳細資料在連部 - 是，長官
Shall we finish the game, Mr. Hall?
把棋下完怎樣，霍爾先生？
As you like, sir.
隨你
Sorry.
對不起
I went a bit too far.
我有點過份
I'm damned if I know what Whitehall expects.
真不知道英國政府怎麼想的
"Don't move too aggressively. Thousands of our chaps in German prison camps."
"別太過份了. 我們有很多人在德國戰俘營裡"
And I quite agree.
這我贊成
"But can't you maintain order there, Major Perry?"
"但你就不能維持那裡的秩序嗎, 佩裡上校?"
And when I ask for troop reinforcements, they send me a single Captain Connor.
我要求增加兵力，他們卻只派來個康納上尉
"Let him have a look at the matter." I mean, oh, dear.
"讓他處理一下這個事情" 我是說, 唉
With those uniforms you look more British than the Guard.
穿上這軍服，你比警衛還像英國人
No one will stop you once you are out of the gate.
沒人會阻攔你出大門
It's our Scottish contact.
是我們的蘇格蘭聯絡人
He'll be waiting for Hochbauer and Schmidt on the Glenfoyle Road.
他在Glenfoyle大街 等Hochbauer和Schmidt
Good.
好
B is for Berlin and breakout.
B 代表柏林和暴動
What did Berlin say?
柏林方面怎麼說?
English. It wasn't Berlin.
說英語 不是柏林
It was our friend here in Scotland...
是我們這裡的蘇格蘭朋友
and he agrees to an earlier meeting with you.
他同意提前見你
Let's raise a little hell when Perry tries to put on the handcuffs...
佩裡要我們帶手銬時 我們大鬧一場
and you can march straight off and join the British army.
你可以直接出去，混進英國人中
We used to have picnics here when I first came. It was grand.
我剛來時我們常在這裡野炊 很棒的
They were so lonely, the German lads, and they were so nice.
德國小伙子很孤獨，很可愛
Then they made the rule, I guess. Closed the camp tight.
然後制定了規定，縮緊了營地
When was that?
什麼時候的事?
About a year ago, when the headmaster came.
有一年吧，頭來的時候
Uh, the Major. Major Perry, that is.
呃, 是上校 佩裡上校, 是的
When Major Perry came, sir.
佩裡上校來的時候
You're a bunch of weaklings.
一幫弱不經風的傢伙
Now it's the Lufwaffe's turn.
該空軍的了
Good morning, Captain Schleutter.
早晨好, Schleutter上尉
Thank you for the list you sent me this morning.
謝謝你早晨送來了名單
But there are others of us who speak excellent English.
但還有其他英語講得很好的
Your English is excellent, Kranz.
你英語很好, Kranz
The tunnel was begun before you came here.
地道在你來前就開始挖了
Your list, the 28 men who are to escape, are all U-boat men.
名單上要逃離的人28人 都是潛艇上的人
None of my men. None of Unger's engineers.
沒我的人，也沒有Unger上的技師
I took the tunnel over on orders from Hitler and Doenitz.
我掌控地道 是受命於希特勒和Doenitz
In order to get skilled U-boat men back into the war.
是為了讓有技術的潛艇人員返回戰爭
Germany must have them now.
德國現在需要他們
I understand, but my men want some explanation.
我明白, 但我的人需要些解釋
You're a Luftwaffe Commandant. Do you explain orders?
你是空軍司令官 你解釋命令嗎？
I want some explanation about the way you treated Neuchl.
我要你解釋為何那樣對待Neuchl
That flying fairy, Hauptman, he's a bad German.
那個仙女，他是個德國孬種
Yes, I've spent a very decent holiday or two in lreland.
是的，我在愛爾蘭度過一兩個很愜意的假
What made you decide to suspend the outside privileges for the Germans?
為什麼中止了戰俘在外活動的待遇?
I felt that my predecessor had taken too many liberties with regulations.
我覺得我前任對制度太隨意了
As a matter of fact, Von Westhofen agreed with me--
事實上,Von Westhofen 和我協議--
the German senior officer in the camp until his death last April.
是營中官銜最高的 直到他4月份死去
Nice old boy, General Von Westhofen.
好老頭, Von Westhofen將軍
A great feeling for books.
很愛看書
Complete opposite of the young devil now in command. You've heard of Schleutter?
現在是個年輕的魔鬼負責 你聽說過Schleutter嗎？
Yes. What did the nice old boy die of?
聽說過。那老頭怎麼死的？
- A natural death? - Heart attack.
- 自然死亡? - 心臟病發作
Morning.
早安
Captain Connor's been sent up from London.
康納上尉是倫敦派來的
He's to assist me in analyzing the problems here.
他來協助我分析這裡的情況
When are you goin' to lift your 48-hour siege, sir?
48小時的處罰什麼時候結束？
Tomorrow morning at reveille.
明早起床號時
- Let's have a look inside then. - I think not, Captain.
- 我們進去看看 - 不要, 上尉
It would weaken the effect of the punishment.
會減弱處罰的效果
I should have a look around.
我要四處看看
Captain, 12 men were seriously injured in there yesterday.
上尉, 昨天在那裡有12個人受重傷
If you go in, it's your responsibility.
若你進去，是你的責任
Yes, sir.
好的
- Does that phone go to all the towers? - Yes, sir.
- 那電話通所有崗樓嗎? - 是的長官
Excuse me.
對不起
This is Captain Connor speaking.
我是康納上尉
I'm comin' inside now.
我要進去了
Will you come along, Mr. Cox?
你也來好嗎, 考科斯先生?
Reinforcements - one more man!
增援 - 一個新人!
Looks like we have company.
看來我們來客了
What do you suppose Von Westhofen died of, Mr. Cox?
你認為Von Westhofen 怎麼死的, 考科斯先生?
I expect it was as Major Perry said, sir.
就像佩裡上校所說，先生
I'd like your opinion on that.
我想知道你的看法
Well, he always seemed in the best of health to me, sir.
我看他一直很健康
You think Schleutter got rid of him?
你認為Schleutter除掉了他?
The bastard has control now. That's all I know.
那狗娘養的控制了這裡 我就知道這些
- Have you had any escapes? - A few.
- 有人逃走過嗎? - 有幾個
Most of them get picked up in the local whorehouse.
大多數在妓院被抓回來
A couple did make it across to the lrish Free State.
有兩人成功地逃到了愛爾蘭自由州
Hell, you say. Horrible place to wind up.
你是說地獄吧 去了可怕的地方
There's only one way to handle prisoners, sir.
只有一個辦法對付戰犯
Lock 'em up someplace so tight...
把他們關進足夠小的的地方
that all they can do is eat, sleep and shit.
使他們只能吃、睡和拉屎.
But the Geneva Convention wouldn't abide it.
但日內瓦協議不容許
Do they have any workshops?
他們有工場嗎？
They can make almost anything you care to name.
他們可以製造出你說的任何東西
Made uniforms as good as new for their top officers.
把他們軍官的軍服搞得像新的一樣
They've got the lot: tinkers, tailors.
他們有焊鍋匠、裁縫
-Candlestick makers, I shouldn't wonder. -Did they make any guns yet?
- 造燭台的, 我不奇怪 - 他們造過槍嗎?
We search, we try to surprise them. We find nothing.
我們搜過，突然搜查，什麼也沒找到
It turns out we always get the surprises.
好像我們總是在詫異
- Is that Schleutter? - Ay, number one barracks.
- 那是Schleutter嗎? - 是, 一號房
To be sure.
肯定
"Quiet Willi."
"沉默的威利"
His men aren't so quiet, though. He's seen to that.
而他的人並不沉默 是他負責
He's got more authority here than he ever had on a U-boat.
他得到了比在潛艇上更大的權力.
I heard about his playin' at war games yesterday.
我昨天聽說了他在軍事演習中的表現
- Exciting, was it? - You're dead right, sir.
- 很刺激，是不是? - 太對了，長官
That's the mess hall up there. Around the corner is the cooler.
那裡是食堂。拐角處是冷卻器
The Major hasn't made enough use of it yet, sir.
上校還沒充分利用它
Are you irritated by this lot?
有這幫人你煩不煩？
- I could do without them, sir. - Quick march, then.
- 沒他們更好，長官 - 那就走快點
That's lovely topsoil, Willi.
表層土很好, 威利
Were you satisfied with your turnip inspection, Captain?
對你的蘿蔔視察滿意嗎, 上尉?
Just grand.
很滿意
You're not puttin' the dirt from your tunnel there, are you?
你把地道的土放在那裡，是不是？
Tunnel? You're old-fashioned, Captain.
地道? 你過時了, 上尉
That's right.
沒錯
Yes, there must be a better way than that.
是的, 肯定有比地道更好的辦法
Attention, please.
請注意
This is Major Perry.
我是佩裡上校
I am assigning Captain Connor officer in charge of roll call tomorrow morning.
我指派康納上尉負責明天的點名
He will supervise the selection and handcuffing...
他將監督挑選和上手銬
of 25 German officers immediately after roll call.
點名後25名軍官帶手銬
Thank you.
謝謝
There must be a better way.
該有更好的辦法
We keep this entrance from N.2. barracks clear...
我們把這入口與2號房隔開
...since it is the main escape hatch.
因為這是主要的逃跑入口
If you will follow me to No.3.
若你跟我去3號
You can inspect the Attic there.
就能看到頂層
Careful climbing through the latrine closet.
過廁所時小心
There is no light until the Attic.
到頂層才有光
I have calculated the load on the ceiling.
我計算過天花板的負荷
We have 17,000 cubic centimeters of dirt.
我們有1千7百立方厘米的垃圾
I've installed cable supports...
我用繩索來固定
...crude but effective.
粗糙但有效
It's difficult with the advanced schedule.
在預計時間內很難完成
We don't have the incentive of being among those to escape.
在逃跑的人中沒有激勵機制
Of course solving the problem is incentive enough for me.
當然，解決這個問題要給我足夠的獎勵
I am an engineer.
我是工程師
Be a fast engineer, Unger.
做個效率高的工程師, Unger
We are five meters from the fence...
我們距籬笆5米
...and 26 meters from the stream.
距河流26米
We will have to use the roof space in Barracks 2.
我們要用2號房的房頂空間
Barracks 3 will soon be filled.
3號房就要裝滿了
- Good evening, Mr. Cox. - Good evening, sir.
- 早晨好, 考科斯先生 - 早晨好，長官
- You ordered reveille at 0600 hours. - That's right.
- 你下令6點吹起床號 - 是的
And C Company to fall out with 25 handcuffs.
C連25人帶手銬
Right.
對
And call the fire brigade, will you?
叫消防隊, 好嗎？
- Fire brigade. - Sir.
- 消防隊 - Sir.
Divide them between the front two ranks.
把他們從前兩個等級分開
Two to each rank.
每級別兩個
Half left, wheel.
半面左轉
Right wheel!
右轉!
This is Captain Connor speaking.
我是康納上尉
To all prisoners: There'll be immediate roll call.
所有犯人聽著: 要立即點名
I repeat: There'll be an immediate roll call and 25 men will be handcuffed.
重複: 立即點名，25人要帶手銬
Enter the barracks as previously instructed.
按計劃進入營地
Move!
行動!
Nobody here, sir. Dead empty. Mother Hubbard.
沒人, 長官. 空的
Same here, sir.
這裡也是，長官
Proceed with caution.
小心檢查
Six men to hut two. On the double!
6人去2號，跑步!
Move in quickly.
快進去
Get back!
回來!
You don't have to make it look this realistic.
不要太認真了
Take it easy, you don't have to kill me.
放鬆點, 你不必殺我的
Hey, you two men!
你們兩個!
Get back!
回來!
Good, now get in there and mix with the British.
好, 去那裡，混進英國人裡
Jerry's taking the bait.
Jerry上鉤了
Watch out, the swines have called the Fire Brigade.
注意, 這豬叫了消防隊
Hurry.
快
Mr. Cox, turn it on!
考科斯, 打開!
It's time for the Luftwaffe. Get Neuchl.
該空軍出來了，帶Neuchl來
Four men with me.
4人跟我來
Get that man!
抓住那人!
Handcuff the bastards.
銬上那狗娘養的
Mr. Cox, that'll do.
考科斯, 行了
Off!
關了!
You seem to have won an argument over handcuffs, Captain.
看來你贏了手銬的爭執, 上尉
And you got all wet, Willi.
你都濕透了, 威利
Have your men out in one hour for roll call.
讓你的人1小時後點名
I insist on visiting your infirmary immediately...
我堅持立刻去醫院
to see to the condition of my men.
看看我的人的情況
Right after the roll call, Willi.
點名後才行, 威利
- And speak English. - Okay.
- 說英語 - 好的
I'm glad to be out too. But we have to find our chum in Cathness.
我也很高興出來。但我們必須找到 在Cathness的朋友
What the hell is he sayin'?
他在說什麼?
I think he's unconscious, sir.
我想他是昏迷了，長官
When he comes around I want to talk to him.
他醒後我要和他講話
- Do whatever you have to. - Do my best.
- 不惜代價 - 我盡力
That man's in a very bad way. Our chaps didn't have to go that far.
那人狀況很差 我們的人沒必要那麼過份
It wasn't them that did it to him.
不是我們的人打的
It was his own lot. Damn near killed him.
是他們自己人，幾乎殺了他
Working off some private grudge, perhaps.
或許出於私人恩怨
Sir, this just came.
長官，剛收到的
Keep a close guard on him, Sergeant. I don't want anyone near him.
派一個人守著他 不要讓任何人接近他
- Captain Connor. - Sir.
- 康納上尉 - 長官
The Germans have taken the handcuffs off our men.
德國人不再銬我們的人了
- Yes, I knew about that. - You knew?
- 是的，我知道了 - 你知道?
I knew before I left London.
離開倫敦前就知道了
Then those men must be unshackled at once.
那些人的手銬要立即拿掉
Not just yet, sir.
不急，長官
Captain, I'm instructed to cooperate with you, not relinquish my command.
上尉, 我受命與你合作 並不是放棄指揮權
Not at all, sir.
不是, 長官
But you see, you must comply with what the lntelligence mission requires.
但你必須按情報部的要求做
And I didn't come here just to put down a riot.
何況我來這裡並非只為解決暴亂問題
Are you formally requesting me to contravene the Geneva Convention?
你在正式要求我違犯日內瓦協議?
For a few hours is all.
只是幾個小時
Very well, Captain Connor.
好吧, 康納上尉
I'm sure today's episode can only redound to your credit.
我相信今日之事對你極有好處
Sir.
長官
I want a complete list of the numbers and injuries to our men.
我要一個所有受傷人員的名單
Eighty present and correct, sir.
現場80人，無誤，長官
Carry on, Sergeant.
繼續，軍士
Sir, checked parade four. All present and accounted for.
長官, 4隊檢查完畢 全部在場，點名完畢
Parade, dismiss!
解散!
I have permission to check on the condition of my men.
我有許可去看望我的人
Yes, sir. Go inside, please.
請進
These look like knife cuts.
這此看起來象刀傷
He lost a lot of blood. Put him to bed.
他失去很多血，把他放床上
Where's Neuchl?
Neuchl呢?
In that little room.
在那小房間裡
- Does the music bother you, sir? - Not at all.
- 音樂讓你煩嗎, 長官? - 沒有
It's a therapy, of course, sir. Germans are fond of this kind of thing.
是為了治療, 長官 德國人喜歡這類
I've always collected classical music because--
我一直在收集古典音樂，因為--
Have you any of that medical brandy?
你有醫用白蘭地嗎?
Y es, sir.
有，長官
Will you have a drink, Captain?
喝一杯嗎, 上尉?
Do I understand you refuse me the right to see one of my men?
為什麼不讓我看一個我的人？
- Just the one brandy, Corporal, please. - Y es, sir.
- 一杯白蘭地，下士 - 是，長官
Well, he doesn't seem to be too anxious to see you.
他並不急於見你的
He got away from those brutes of yours, didn't he?
他逃離了你的那幫畜生，對不？
They nearly killed him.
他們幾乎殺了他
He's under the care of the chief surgeon.
他由首席外科醫生看護
You lrish are just fabulous, Captain.
你這愛爾蘭人真是不可思議, 上尉
You really have got that famous lrish imagination.
你真是繼承了著名的愛爾蘭想像力
But your water sports this morning made such a confusion.
但你今早的水造成了如此混亂
Who knows what you saw?
誰知道你看見了什麼?
I know what I saw. I saw a man tryin' to escape.
看見了什麼我知道 我看見一個人逃跑
I'm not contradicting you really, Captain.
不是我和你唱反調, 上尉
You may have seen an attempted escape.
你或許看見企圖逃跑
Is it not the duty of all prisoners to try?
哪個犯人不想逃跑?
- Sir. - Thank you, Corporal.
- 長官 - 謝謝, 下士
Toscanini?
Toscanini?
Furtwangler does it better.
Furtwangler 更棒
By the way, the German camps have taken the shackles off the British prisoners.
順便說一下, 德國營已經取消了 英國戰俘的手銬
And we shall reciprocate very soon.
我們會很快做出回應
Of course, your lads did quite a bit of damage.
當然, 你的人造成了不小的破壞
We'll have to deduct that from their pay.
我們將從他們工資裡扣
And that will be all for now, Captain.
眼下就沒事了, 上尉
You'll want to see your men.
你可去看你的人
And Captain, deduct the damages from my pay.
上尉, 扣我的工資補償損失
- Thank you. - You've done too much as it is.
- 謝謝 - 你做的已經夠多了
Keep your eye on that one. See that he leaves soon.
看著那個人，讓他盡快離開
And don't let anyone else in without my authorization.
沒我同意不許任何人進去
There they are.
在這裡
Take these books to the prisoners. I've inspected them.
把這些書帶給犯人 我檢查過了
This is all the Kriegsmariners?
這些都是水手的嗎？
Y es. I separated them.
是的，我分撿出來的
I don't read German all that well.
我看不懂德文
I don't even know what the hell I'm lookin' for.
我甚至不知道我在找什麼
- What's that? - Ewigkeit.
- 那是什麼? - 永恆
"My dear wife, it has seemed like an eternity...
"親愛的妻子, 像是已經隔了很久
since last I kissed your bosom...
自從我上次親你的胸部
and slept with my arms entwined...
擁你而睡
You read these horny letters all day?
你一整天都在讀這種情書？
-That's the function of the post office. -lt is?
-這是郵局的職責 -是嗎?
"The turnip fields are growing, dear...
"蘿蔔長得很好，親愛的
and we are going to do several plays by Shakespeare.
我們還要排練幾部莎士比亞的戲.
I wish I had you with me now to put my arms around and feel your bosom."
真希望你在我身邊 能擁抱你撫摸你的胸部"
Bosom, bosom, bosom.
胸部, 胸部, 胸部
Why do they put that Roman numeral in the date?
為什麼他們在日期前放羅馬數字?
- What date? - The date has a Roman numeral in it.
- 什麼日期? - 有羅馬數字的日期
- You ever notice that? - I never noticed that before.
- 你注意到過嗎? - 以前從沒注意過
He's got that queer little German seven...
有個怪怪的小7
and the one and the two, but it starts off with a Roman numeral.
還有1和2, 但用羅馬數字開頭
We're gonna get us a code man down here from London...
就要有個倫敦的破譯人員來這裡
and have him take a look at these horny letters.
讓他看看這些情書
Get back to bed! Do you hear me?
回床上去! 聽到沒有?
Look out! They've got a hostage! Get back to your beds immediately!
注意! 他們有個人質! 馬上回到床上去!
Have I kept you waitin', Willi?
我讓你久等了嗎, 威利?
It's your prison, Captain. We follow your orders.
這是你的監獄, 上尉 我們聽你的命令行事
You have imposed your kind of order, haven't you?
你下達了你的命令，沒有嗎?
- Did you know him well? - No.
- 你和他熟嗎? - 不
What's his name? You know that.
他叫什麼名字? 你知道的
Rupert Neuchl.
魯珀特 Neuchl
You have it on your hospital report.
在你們的醫院記錄中有
I mean, he must have regained consciousness during the day.
我是說, 他在日間肯定甦醒過的
He hanged himself.
他上吊死了
Do you want to write that to his family, or should I do it?
你要那樣通知他家人，還是我來？
It won't be necessary.
那沒必要
- Why'd he hang himself? - He was weak.
- 他為何上吊? - 他懦弱
He was a homosexual. Why do you ask me?
他是同性戀。為何問我?
We asked everyone else in the ward. They didn't see anything, of course.
我們問了病房中所有的人 當然他們什麼也沒看見
You're the commanding officer. Why'd he die?
你是負責人，他為什麼要死?
Captain, he died under your custody.
上尉, 他死在你的監禁中
I smell cognac, I think.
我想我聞到了白蘭地
You smell lrish whiskey, I think.
我想你是聞到了愛爾蘭威士忌
- There you are. - Thank you.
- 給你 - 謝謝
It's a pity the corpse never enjoys the wake.
很遺憾，屍體總不能與守靈人同樂
A hell of a nice fellow to talk to, though.
在黃泉路上也有個好人聊天
Here's to you, Rupert.
你喝點, 魯珀特
Your German-- you're pronouncing it very good today.
你的德語-- 你今天發音很好
You're pronouncin' your English very good too.
你的英語發音也很好
Where'd you learn English, Willi?
你在哪裡學的英語, 威利?
Bremen UnterZeeboot Academie, ten years ago.
Bremen UnterZeeboot學院, 10年了
- How old are you? - Twenty-seven.
- 你多大? - 27
You must've had a couple of years in the Hitler Youth Camp then, with some luck.
那你就有幸在希特勒衝鋒隊干幾年了
A lot of luck.
很幸運
Two years.
2年
And you?
你呢?
Me what?
我什麼?
- I mean, how old? - I'm 44.
- 多大? - 44.
- Still very much alive. - I'm quite well, thanks.
- 還很健康 - 我很好，謝謝
I mean, your new command is very much impressed.
你這新官給人印象深刻
One of those nice elderly British guards told me today...
有個衛兵今天告訴我
you were a hell of a journalist.
你是個惹麻煩的記者
That's true. I'm a hell of a journalist. I could make you famous, Willi.
沒錯，我是個惹麻煩的記者 我可讓你出名, 威利
Now why don't you tell the lively old crime reporter why the man's dead?
那為不告訴我這老不死的記者 這人為何而死呢？
You expect me to tell you that I killed him, and why?
你想讓我說我殺了他，為什麼？
No, you don't have to.
不，不必你做
I can see your pleasure in the kill.
我可看出你樂於殺人
Can you?
是嗎?
Perhaps you can see somebody who believes in the war...
或許你可看見一個相信勝利
who believes in his people, his leaders.
相信他的人民和上司的人
We kill in a war for those things, huh?
我們為此而在戰爭中殺戮, 是不?
But maybe you don't.
或許你不是
I mean, you're lrish and you're a captain in the British army.
我是說，你作為一個愛爾蘭人 卻在英國軍隊當上尉
That same British army that has killed your own lrish people for centuries.
這只英國軍隊已經殺你愛爾蘭同胞幾個世紀
What do you really believe in? What kind of order?
你到底信仰什麼? 聽誰的命令?
What laws do you obey?
信誰的法律?
Well, I obey as few laws as I have to.
嗯, 我只服從不得不服從的法律
And I'm not much of a one for order.
我也不是個循規蹈矩的人
It has to be, I suppose...
我想是順其自然吧
but there's order and then there's order, isn't there?
但規矩就是規矩，是不是？
Death is a kind of order, isn't it?
死也是一種規矩，對不？
I mean, Neuchl there, he's all in order now.
我是說, Neuchl 他現在很守規矩
But, Willi, that's an awful lot of shit about your people.
但是威利, 你的人很不地道
You've killed two of them that I know of.
就我所知，你殺了2個人
That's not true.
那不對
You killed him and you probably killed your commanding officer as well.
你殺了他，可能也殺了你的上司
And for that I'm goin' to see you hang.
我看你要為此受鉸刑
You enjoy killing too, huh?
你也樂於殺人吧?
- Mr. Cox. - Do you not, Captain Connor?
- 考科斯先生 - 不是嗎, 康納上尉?
See that the Captain's escorted back to his quarters, if you please.
護送上尉去營地
Gate, gentlemen!
開門!
Connor wants me to think that Neuchl told him something.
康納想讓我以為Neuchl跟他說了什麼
I don't think it was much. I'm not sure.
我想沒什麼，但說不准
'28 Submariners' Connor said to me in German.
康納用德語對我說 '28水手'
My God!
上帝!
He will do nothing for the moment.
他現在也沒招
But he'll try to prove I killed Neuchl.
但他會證明我殺了Neuchl
Meanwhile we go ahead of schedule.
我們要提前
Hochbauer and Schmidt won't be back until Friday.
Hochbauer和Schmidt星期五才回來
The tunnel won't reach the stream for five days.
地道5天內挖不到小河
Tell Unger not to go to the stream.
告訴Unger不挖到小河
Divert and go under the Guard house.
轉向警衛房下面
It's much shorter.
那短多了
Don't let the men know it.
別讓人知道
Go ahead of schedule.
要提前
That's our contact.
是我們的聯絡人
Can I give you boys a lift?
坐順路車嗎?
What are they writing home about, Lieutenant?
他們寫些什麼, 中尉?
I can't really tell yet.
我還不知道
It's a question of assembling the basic code pattern. As you see--
像是機器碼，如你所見--
- When will you know anything? - Hard to say.
- 什麼時候能好? - 很難說
Could be a day, could be a week if there are variations.
一天，若有變異，也許要一週
But we don't have to wait for a decoded message to know that we have trouble.
但我們不必靠破譯知道有麻煩
Obviously Schleutter's at the center of it.
顯然是Schleutter策劃的
We must transfer him to Blackpool.
我們要把他移去Blackpool
- I need him here a bit longer. - You need him?
- 我需要他再呆這裡一段時間 - 你需要他?
He's at the center, but of what? I can't find out if he's in Blackpool.
他策劃的，但策劃的什麼? 若他去Blackpool我就查不出來了
You must block the old tunnel and be as quick as you can with this one.
你必須盡快阻塞舊地道
Lousy work but necessary.
討厭的事，但必須做
Have you met any resistance in the barracks, Mr. Cox?
你在營地遇到麻煩嗎, 考科斯?
Nothing? Good.
沒有? 好
Well, inform me directly if anything at all happens.
不管發生任何事都要直接通知我
Y es. Thank you, Sergeant Major.
是. 謝謝, 上校
Come in, Captain Connor. I think you ought to know we're onto something.
進來, 康納上尉 我想你應該知道我們在幹什麼
Thank you.
謝謝
It appears that 28 submariners are due to escape.
像是有28個水手想逃跑
There's a U-boat coming to pick them up.
有艘潛艇來接他們
"U-841 available. Assign 28 men. Location, date agreeable."
"可用U-841. 派28人. 地點時間同意"
- What's the location and date? - We checked all the letters.
- 地點時間呢? - 我們查了所有的信
Specific time must've been set before in something they received earlier.
約定的時間肯定在以前收到的東西裡
It doesn't matter. We'll move in now and break it up.
沒關係，我們現在就進去阻止他們
There's got to be a tunnel. We'll pull every barracks apart until we find it.
肯定有地道，寧可拆除所有房子也要找到它
Lieutenant, could you excuse us a minute, please?
中尉, 請出去一會好嗎？
Go and have a cup of coffee or something.
去喝杯咖啡之類的
What if we were to let 'em go?
讓他們走怎麼樣？
Then we could follow and find out where the rendezvous is and land the sub.
這樣我們可跟蹤找到集合點和潛艇
How'd Willi like that?
威利會喜歡嗎?
Permit the escape?
准許逃跑?
The tunnel's got to come up within 50 yards of that fence.
地道出口肯定在圍牆50碼之內
All we have to do is put patrols out there, see where they come through.
我們只要派出巡邏，看他們從哪裡出來
We keep radio contact.
我們保持無線電聯繫
Then we inform the military and civilian police all the way out to the coast.
然後通知軍隊和地方警察 一直佈置到海岸
Then we nab the sub and the whole lot.
最後搶奪潛艇，抓住犯人
My job is to run this camp and account for the prisoners in it.
我的職責是管理戰俘營 負責裡面的戰俘
And curiously enough that doesn't include letting 28 of them escape...
奇怪的是那並不包括允許28人逃走
to further your military career, Captain.
來延長你的軍隊生涯, 上尉
Under my instructions at this moment, our men are searching German barracks.
現在，我們的人正在按我的命令 搜索德國監捨
- Perry. - It's Major Perry, Captain!
- 佩裡 - 是佩裡上校, 上尉!
I'm your superior officer and you will respect the rank.
我是你的上級，你應該尊重官銜
I don't give a damn about your bloody rank, or anyone else's.
我才不管你什麼官銜，或任何人的
I got sent up here to do a job.
我被派來是執行任務
I'm supposed to find out what's behind that break.
我要查出暴亂背後的陰謀
If you don't like what I'm doing, call General Kerr and have him relieve me.
若你不贊成我的作法 就打電話給克爾將軍中止我的工作
Now bring the men back and stop that search.
把人叫回來，停止搜索
The War Office has given you a unique authority here.
作戰部給了你特權
I suppose I must yield to it.
我想我必須服從
Even though I believe you to be mistaken and an arrogant fool.
儘管我相信你是錯的 並且你是個自負的傻瓜
I'll give the order, Captain.
我來下命令, 上尉
Then I'll phone London and have them remove one of us...
然後給倫敦打電話 讓他們調走我們之一
from this intolerable situation.
避開這難以忍受的狀況
Search has been called off. Everything back.
搜索取消了，東西放回
Why give up the search, Captain?
為什麼放棄搜索, 上尉?
Sir! There's something in here you ought to see, sir.
長官! 有件東西你該看看
And this one's just been sick, sir.
說這人一直在生病，長官
Mr. Cashman, we'll have a roll call.
Cashman, 我們要點名
Yes, sir. Carry on, Sergeant.
是，長官 繼續, 軍士
- How long have they been away with-- - Who?
- 他們走了多久了 - 誰?
I want the names of these two that escaped.
給我這兩個逃犯的名字
Sorry. I didn't know them personally.
對不起，我不認識他們
Seal off the barracks until further orders.
封鎖營地，等待命令
It's very likely to be a long roll call, Willi.
看來點名要很久的, 威利
Submarines do well in water, not the Luftwaffe.
潛艇在海上幹得不錯，空軍不行
Give it up, Schluetter.
放棄吧, Schluetter
17 hours.
17 小時
The truck will be close enough to signal.
潛艇能近得收到信號
You mean to go tonight?
你是說今晚走?
Soldier!
士兵!
I want to speak to Sergeant Major Cox.
我要和考科斯上校講話
Captain Schleutter gave us the names of the two men who escaped.
Schleutter上尉交出了2逃犯的名單
He's instructed his men to stand by for roll call.
他下令他的人配合點名
Why the hell does he bother to knuckle under now?
為什麼他現在屈服了？
I'll get identifications on the wire, sir.
我去拿花名冊
Guards. Open the barracks and let the bastards in out of the rain.
衛兵，打開監捨 讓這幫狗娘養的進去避雨
It's been an uncomfortable day gentlemen.
不舒服的一天，先生們
Dry off.
晾乾
You never stop, eh Captain?
你總是沒完, 上尉?
What are your plans for tomorrow?
你明天的計劃是什麼？
First a meal and dreams of warm women.
先吃飯，然後做夢會女人
The damn fool doesn't care if we all get pneumonia.
這他媽的蠢蛋 根本不管我們是否會得肺炎
Shut up!
住口!
Don't hang yourself like Neuchl.
別象Neuchl那樣找死
Tell the men that we go right after lights out.
通知有關人熄燈後走
We should wait until Connor is less alert.
我們應該等康納不太警覺時
We don't have to go tonight.
今晚不走也行的
Connor will have this hands full in this barracks tonight.
康納的人手今晚都在監捨裡
We meet in No. 2 barracks an hour after lights out.
熄燈後1小時我們在2號房見
Are we going to make it?
能完成嗎?
We've almost finished.
快完成了
The rain has put a bad strain on the support.
這雨的壓力很大
We'll be alright, I'm sure.
我們會好的，我肯定
Pour us a drink, Mr. Cox.
給我們倒杯酒, 考科斯
Take some of that from the stores and give it to the lads outside.
給外面的夥計送些去
Thank you, sir. The old sweats'll appreciate that.
謝謝長官，他們會感謝的
In the morning get me that friend of Neuchl's-- what's his name--
早晨把Neuchl的朋友帶來 他叫什麼來著
Lieutenant Berger.
Berger中尉
Help!
救命!
Guards! Come on out of there! Come on. Move, move!
衛兵! 快出來! 快，快!
Let's have you! Go look on the other side!
到我們這裡來! 去看看另一邊!
Come on!
快!
- Which one? - I don't know.
- 哪裡? - 我不知道
Hello, towers. Which one?
塔樓，幾號房?
Barracks three. Looks like the whole damned thing caved in.
3號房，像是整個房子陷進去了
Thanks.
謝謝
Bloody hell!
見他媽的鬼!
Come on. Out of the bloody way! Move! Out! Out!
快. 別他媽的擋路! 快! 快!
Right. Let's get through this rubbish.
對，搬開這些垃圾
What are you looking at? Get moving.
你在看什麼? 繼續走
Go - quietly - Go!
走 - 安靜 - 走!
Patrols Able, Baker, Charlie, keep in radio contact with me and the main gate.
Able、Baker、Charlie 與我和大門保持無線聯繫
Give us an axe.
拿斧子來
Get an axe and smash the other door down.
拿斧子劈開其它門
Get this lot back in their beds and count 'em.
讓這些人回床位，查舖
Get the men back to their beds for a check.
讓這些人回床檢查
Now Holtz - collapse it!
Holtz - 弄塌它!
Clumsy idiot, you could have killed us all.
笨蛋, 你差點把我們都弄死了
Six dead so far, sir.
已經死了6人，長官
Find the damned tunnel.
找到該死的地道
- What the hell's going on now? - I don't exactly know, sir.
- 發生了什麼事? - 我不太清楚，長官
- Number three's roof's collapsed. - The roof's collapsed?
- 3號房房頂塌了 - 房頂塌了?
Y es, sir.
是的，長官
Captain Connor's up there now, sir.
康納上尉現在那裡
Is he? Has he checked round his exterior patrols?
是嗎? 他派的外部巡邏檢查了沒?
- Not as far as I know, sir. - Do that now.
- 還沒有，長官 - 現在去做
Drive on.
繼續開
You men get the stretcher.
你們去拿擔架
I'll see if they've got the count, sir.
我看看他們查完沒有
Sergeant, get back down to the main gate and get a three-tonner here for wounded.
軍士，到大門來，搞個3噸的運傷員
- Have you got the count yet? - Not yet, Major.
- 查完了沒有? - 還沒有, 上校.
Only ten dead, Connor.
只死了10人, 康納
Thirty-seven not accounted for.
37人失蹤
I think we've located the tunnel, sir.
我想我們找到了地道，長官
Hold it. It's collapsed.
別進. 塌了
Yes, sir. Ten dead.
是長官，死了10人
Another 27 trapped when the tunnel collapsed.
另有27人在地道塌陷時被困
Presumably Captain Schleutter was with them.
估計Schleutter上尉和他們在一起
No, sir. It'll take several hours of digging.
不, 長官. 要挖幾個小時
It needn't have happened. I'm sending you a complete report in a few hours.
本來可避免的，幾小時後我送給你詳細報告
No, sir. He hasn't accomplished a thing.
不, 長官. 他沒完成什麼
You may inform General Kerr that Captain Connor's mission here...
你可以告訴克爾將軍 康納上尉來這裡執行任務
has been a fatal mistake.
是個致命錯誤
Good night, sir.
晚安長官
Nothing, sir. Not a bloody one of them!
沒人，長官 他媽的一個人也沒有!
Base Station Five. This is Connor.
5號基地，我是康納
Give us a police frequency.
給我警察的頻道
Roadblock in position on A85.
A85號地路障已設
Police report no suspicious traffic on the B828...
警察報告B828路段沒有可疑的車
and continue mobile patrols north.
正繼續向北巡邏
All units.
所有單位
Per the McKenzie break, escaped prisoners should be considered armed.
McKenzie騷亂, 逃跑的犯人可能有武器
All units station traffic, please copy.
所有交警單位請注意
Northeast of Perth and Aberfeldy...
Perth和Aberfeldy東北
east to Dunfermline...
東至Dunfermline...
south to Falkirk...
南至Falkirk...
southwest to Glasgow, west to lnverary.
西南至Glasgow, 西至lnverary.
The following roadblocks will go into effect in the immediate area--
下列路障即刻啟用--
Number 33 between McKenzie and Stirling.
McKenzie和Stirling之間的33號
This is Glengarry police.
這裡是Glengarry警局
We require extra mobiles to maintain watch on coast road.
我們需要更多的車輛 檢查沿海路段
Glengarry police, over.
Glengarry警局, 完畢
North Shore coast guards.
北海岸警隊
Coastal Command.
空軍海防總隊
We have no response from northern moorland's road net.
我們沒收到moorland北部地段的報告
Presumably still in effect from the Southern Lochs...
估計在檢查南湖
as far north as Loch Glenny.
至Glenny湖北部
Case section at Clough here. All units please reply.
所有單位請回答
Please, repeat, all units.
重複，所有單位
- Sir! General Kerr's arrived. - Oh, God.
- 長官! 克爾將軍來了 - 上帝
- What happened? - Balls-up, sir. Simple as that.
- 發生了什麼? - 混亂, 長官. 就那麼簡單
Nothing simple about it.
一點也不簡單
Worse than what happened at Bowmanville Camp in Canada last year...
比去年加拿大Bowmanville戰俘營 的事更嚴重
and Whitehall thought that was a disaster.
英國政府認為那是個災難
Perry's made a full report to top staff.
佩裡給總參謀部寫了詳細報告
I don't blame him. I could have prevented it.
我不責怪他，我本可以避免這事的
That's dead right. Now, let's get back, shall we, old chap?
這就是了。現在我們開始吧，老夥計?
I don't care what the priority classification is.
我不管什麼優先級別
I want three more aircraft.
我再要3駕飛機
You're damned right I do.
就是這樣
Coastal Command say there are several thousand miles...
空軍海防總隊說有幾千英里的
of naturally camouflaged coastline around Scotland...
蘇格蘭海岸，並到處是偽裝
and how in the hell can they cover it all.
他們不能搜索遍
Northern moorlands road net-- nothing.
moorlands北部公路網 -- 沒有
There's another call for you, sir.
又一個電話，長官
I'm afraid it's essential to use civilian police, sir.
恐怕必須調用地方警察，長官
- lmportant? - Aye.
- 重要嗎? - 是
Go ahead.
走吧
There's a truck on the A828.
A828號公路上有卡車
Explosives with a police motorcycle escorting it.
爆炸品，由警察摩托車護送
No, sir. Explosives are under the ministry of Fuel and Power.
沒有先生. 爆炸品由燃料動力部管
The escort duty our men are assigned to is never for...
在戰時從不安排
industrial or mining purposes during wartime.
工業或礦上護送任務
- We never assign men for-- - Thanks very much.
- 我們從不派人-- - 非常感謝
Base Section, this is Zero 468.
基地，這是零468
I'm over Ballachulish. All clear, turning south.
我在Ballachulish上空 沒有情況，轉向北部
There's an explosives truck with a motorcycle escort...
有輛警察摩托車護送的裝爆炸品的卡車
heading north on Highway B828.
駛向B828號公路
Stay up there. Don't move in close.
呆在那裡，不要靠近
Roger.
Roger
Let's lose him - turn right in here.
離開他 - 轉向右
They're either goin' for the Firth of Lorne or else Loch Linnhe.
他們或者去Lorne峽灣或者去Linnhe
And they're gonna lead us right to the sub.
他們將帶我們找到潛艇
Straight away. Splendid.
直接到. 太好了
It has to come to the surface and move in to the beach, doesn't it?
它必須浮出水面和靠近海灘，是嗎？
Y eah, but if we miss them, we've had it.
是的，但若找不到他們就有我們受的了
Bag them now and call that good.
抓住他們，就沒事了
- I have lost contact with the truck. - Ben, for God's sake.
- 我看不到卡車了 - 上帝保佑
It's the reconnaissance pilot. He's lost contact.
是偵察機，他失去目標
Quick - get rid of that.
快 - 扔了這個
Lost contact.
失去目標
Suggest immediate police surveillance north on Highway B828.
建議警察監視B828公路北部
- I'll get a plane myself. - I'll arrange transport, sir.
- 我去找飛機 - 我安排運輸, 長官
Where are you men going?
你們這些人去哪裡?
Just going to make our Yank visitors comfy, Dad.
去讓我們的美國佬舒服些，老爹.
Load of furniture...
全是傢俱...
for the C.O. at the new American base at Mahaddie.
運給Mahaddie的美國新基地
Look.
看
Even a shower attachment for the silly bastard.
甚至有給那幫傢伙的淋浴
It's five shillings.
要5先令
Heave up the tail! Good man.
開船! 好人
Won't be able to see a bloody thing after dark.
天黑後什麼也看不見
Look-outs up there.
去那邊察看
All clear.
沒事
Camouflage the truck.
偽裝卡車
This is White Lady 7.
這是白女士7號
You are on a navy frequency, Flight 43. I have no authorization--
你在用海軍頻道，43號機 我沒有授權 --
I know that. I'm just tellin' you the sub will surface and sit there.
我知道. 我正要告訴你 潛艇將浮出且停在那裡
Have any idea where that might be?
知不知道會在哪裡?
Hell, no. If I knew, I wouldn't be guessin'.
不知道. 我若知道就不用猜了
That's a waste of time.
這是浪費時間
Let's drive it down this hole and get going.
把它推進洞裡快走
The boats first.
船先到
Have you gone crazy?
你瘋了嗎?
Stop the truck!
停車!
What the hell is going on?
這他媽的怎麼回事？
Now what the hell?
是他媽的什麼?
Do you see that? Go on down there.
看到了嗎? 下去
Burning rubbish I should say, sir. No sign of anything else.
我想，是燃燒的垃圾，長官 沒其他東西
Go on ahead.
繼續走
This is White Lady 7.
這是白女士7號
I've just completed a sweep of grid 16 X-ray.
我剛完成X光掃瞄
Sunset in 18 minutes.
18分鐘日落
Will turn for home at that time.
到時返航
E.T.A., 1930.
E.T.A., 1930.
Out.
完畢
We have no flight plan for you, Flight 43. Return to base.
我們沒有你的飛行計劃，43號機 返回基地
- I say, you're not authorized. - Where'd you get an idea like that?
- 我說, 你沒經授權 - 你怎麼會那樣想?
- Flight Control. - They're pullin' your leg.
- 飛行控制 - 他們扯你後腿
Make another run offshore like a good fellow and I'll get you a medal.
再飛一圈，我給你搞勳章
Hurry, I'm right behind you.
快, 我在你後面
There's the sub. Jesus, that's it!
潛艇在那兒。上帝，就是它
White Lady, this is Flight 43.
白女士, 這裡是43號機
Sub's off the point about a mile.
潛艇在一英里處
About a mile! U-boat on the surface.
一英里! 浮在海面
Engine, full ahead.
發動, 全速向前
Go on down there. Buzz the hell out of 'em.
下到那裡，震開他們
Will you get in there. It'll submerge on you!
你能到嗎，它要下潛了!
Looks like we've been hit, sir. Better find a place to put her down.
我們好像被擊中了，長官 最好找個地方降落
Asdic reports lost contact with U-boat. Request another sweep.
探測不到潛艇，請示再次掃瞄
This is White Lady 7 calling Madam.
這是白女士7號呼叫夫人
U-boat submerged 1924.
潛艇1924年浮出
Bearing 045 off course head point...
方位045，偏離頂點航線
and boarding four prisoners who were abandoned.
有4個被拋棄的犯人
Will continue asdic sweep on 19 degrees aft from grid 13 easy.
將繼續搜尋
Request assistance.
請求援助
General Kerr calling Captain Connor.
克爾將軍呼叫康納上尉
Come in, Connor.
快接, 康納
This is General Kerr calling Naval Frequency 453.
這是克爾將軍呼叫海軍453頻道.
Willi, looks like we're both in the shit house.
威利, 我們倆都有麻煩了
General Kerr calling Captain Connor.
克爾將軍呼叫康納上尉
Come in, Connor.
快接, 康納